<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QR &amp; Barcode</string>
    <string name="home_title">QR &amp; Barcode Scanner</string>
    <string name="home_footer_message">All core functionality runs locally on your device, with no internet connection required. This app is entirely open source, and its code is available for inspection on GitHub.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_link">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_body">Effective July 17, 2026.\n\nQR &amp; Barcode Scanner is developed by ThinApps.\n\nCamera frames and images selected through Android Photo Picker are processed on your device only to detect QR codes and barcodes. Image content and detected scan results are not sent to ThinApps or Google. The app does not retain camera frames or selected images.\n\nAccepted scan results are automatically stored in the app’s private local history together with a timestamp. History remains on your device until you clear it from the Scan History screen or uninstall the app. ThinApps does not receive, sell, or share your scan content or local history.\n\nThe app uses Google’s ML Kit Barcode Scanning SDK. ML Kit may collect limited technical information, such as device and app information, a per-installation identifier, API configuration and usage, performance information, event types, and error codes, for diagnostics and usage analytics. This technical information does not include camera frames, selected images, detected scan results, or local scan history.\n\nThe app has no accounts, advertising, or cloud storage. Barcode scanning works without an internet connection.\n\nCopy, Open, and Share occur only when you choose them. Copy places the selected scan result on Android’s system clipboard. Open passes a supported web address to a compatible app on your device. Share passes the selected result through Android’s system share sheet. External apps and services operate under their own privacy policies.\n\nFor privacy questions, contact ThinApps using the developer contact information shown on QR &amp; Barcode Scanner’s Google Play listing.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_message">Camera permission is required to scan QR codes and barcodes. Scanning happens locally on your device.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_button">Allow Camera</string>
    <string name="scan_status_ready">Point your camera at a QR code or barcode.</string>
    <string name="scan_status_found">Preview the scanned result below.</string>
    <string name="scan_status_permission_needed">Camera permission is needed before scanning.</string>
    <string name="scan_status_camera_error">Error: camera could not start on this device.</string>
    <string name="scan_result_label">Scanned Result</string>
    <string name="scan_result_empty">No QR code or barcode scanned yet.</string>
    <string name="scan_result_open_failed">No app found to open this link.</string>
    <string name="scan_image_no_code">No readable code found.</string>
    <string name="scan_image_read_failed">Could not read that image.</string>
    <string name="history_title">Scan History</string>
    <string name="history_hint">Tap a saved result to preview it again.</string>
    <string name="history_empty">No scan history yet.</string>
    <string name="history_cleared">History cleared</string>
    <string name="action_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="action_open">Open</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="action_scan_from_image">Scan from image</string>
    <string name="action_open_history">Open scan history</string>
    <string name="action_clear_history">Clear All History</string>
    <string name="action_clear_result">Clear scanned result</string>
    <string name="action_torch_on">Turn torch on</string>
    <string name="action_torch_off">Turn torch off</string>
    <string name="action_close">Close</string>
</resources>
